geomarriage.com 2014-09-22

# Privacy Policy – Geomarriage.com | Shadi Online

Privacy Policy of Geo Marriage, no. 1 shadi online site of Pakistan. It describes how we collect and share your information with others in the form of your Profile.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy is derived to demonstrate our sole commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information and data. Geomarriage.com will not sell, distribute, barter or transfer any of your personal identifiable information to companies, organizations or other parties without your permission. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand why we gather the minimal personal information and how we collect it. The policy also reflects our commitment to take all commercially possible and reasonable steps to ensure the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information.

We reserve the right to make changes or alter our privacy policies and such changes or alterations will be posted on our website in timely manner.

**What about your profiles at Geomarriage.com?**

Please keep in mind, this site is only designed to help you to find your life partner online. We just publish profiles of people at our site. We don’t have any kind of mechanism to check any profiles truth. There may be fake profiles that we are unable to check. We are sincere to provide a decent and free service to all Pakistani people specially parents of young girls and boys to find their sons and daughters matches online. We don’t own or promote any profile on priority basis. Latest profiles come at top of our profiles listing page. We can edit website link in your profile to promote our sites. We also can’t guarantee the phone number provided in the profile is true or belongs to the same person.

**About your email address?**

If you make profile at geomarriage.com, then you can receive email from other members. You can also send email to other members. Its totally free service. But if any of the members send spam emails to others then his/her account will be suspended.

**About Your Phone number?**

If you give your phone number while making your profile then it will be shown at your profile. So you may receive calls from others. If you receive un wanted calls then go to your profiles admin area and delete your phone number from there.

**How you receive Communication?**

If you receive any mailing from our side, it means you have profile at out site. If you think you don’t have created your profile at geo marriage, then you should contact us and change password of your email address.

**Unsubscribe Options**

Each email sent has an easy way to unsubscribe from receiving email from the lists you have subscribed to, or to add or modify your mentioned interests. If you wish to unsubscribe, simply contact us for it.

**COOKIES**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third party services to manage analytics of our website. These analytics correspond to the behavior of the visitors on our site. These analytics are collected simply with the aim and objective to further enhance and improve the visitor experience on our site

**Usage of Account Information**

Your private information is safe with us as we will never sell your personal account information or subscriber data with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information you submit to us is only accessible to employees managing the information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for more information.

**What is your duty?**

If you think any of the profile at geomarriage.com is fake or using other persons’s personal information please inform us by visiting our contact us page or directly email us at: geomarriage@yahoo.com, we shall remove it at within 24 working hours.

**How to Contact us**

If you have any queries or questions with regard to our Privacy Policy, kindly visit our contact us page or directly send us email at: geomarriage@yahoo.com
